Hello everyone! I'm in Frankfurt today at a very cool hotel and here I'm visiting
the Amangadista pop-up showroom and fashion presentation. I'm going to walk
as a model but I'm also going to try on some stuff. Check it out!
We have our before the fashion show prosecco and milk schnitten.
That's how models eat.
No, I'm joking.
This is my second runway outfit.
I was just outside for Benno von Stein and now it's Rebellion Fashion and Dino Zardino
and after that, Fernando Buus.
So three fashion presentations tonight.
One after each other.
The other, so oh my gosh.
We were looking for a quiet moment here. I have next to me, what is your model name?
Feline Centrals.
Feline Centrals, I'll link it. But I heard that was your very first show today?
Exactly, exactly. So I was on stage for the first time and ran for wonderful fashion and it was unique.
And how was it? So were you excited?
I was excited, I was full of adrenaline and yes, it was really fun.
Would you do it again?
Definitely.
Yes, you really did!
Yes, totally!
What is your favorite part of the evening?
Or what did you see that was your favorite so far?
I think your shoes are really good!
But also the ones I wear.
Yes, they are also very chic.
And these gloves, amazing!
Hi!
Peachy, how long have we known each other?
At least three or four years.
I'm not quite sure.
We haven't seen each other for a long time.
You still have the running outfit on.
I'm not a fan of Baki anymore.
How are you feeling tonight?
Really, really good.
Good to be back?
Yes, this is the first time I'm at a fetish event for at least one and a half years.
And I'm actually pretty happy that it's such a small event.
What do you normally do when you're not at such events?
I work as a translator, currently also in online marketing and actually also as a model.
And we're having another nice evening now?
We are now definitely!
Hello! Hi!
You may know Ferdinand from my old video when I was in Karlsruhe in the showroom and tried on a lot of boots.
That was a very hot day here.
It's not that hot here, but I ran for you yesterday.
True.
And I wore very nice boots.
Very good.
I tried them on yesterday.
Exactly, our new skis yesterday in the presentation with the extra length and hundreds of sprockets.
I have to count them again.
I always have to try something new when I see Federns and today it will be these here.
Not my color of course, but in fact they sit quite well and do not look so bad.
So, how is it? With one you can't stay.
You have to be number two.
Better than the beige ones, of course, they are black.
And they fit better to the outfit.
I'm here at Rebellion Fashion at the stand.
I had seen the things on the Obsidian for a short time, but you were not at the stand.
I'll introduce myself again.
Gladly.
I'm Bernd from Rebellion Fashion.
Our label has been on the market for four years now.
So relatively young.
I've been in the scene for a little longer, in sales and sales, but I've been
own level set for you.
So of course I had to try a catsuit and I like this one it's really cool with
back here and it's also very comfortable and fits.
I saw her on social media and thought, there are a lot of cool designers out there, let's see what they have to offer.
Have you seen anything you particularly liked?
Oh yes, at Rebellion, there is a body hanging on a golden windowpane, which I think is incredibly beautiful.
I want to try it on.
It's still a secret, it's latex on the outside and fabric on the inside.
And it's a prototype.
I'm always happy when I can try new things.
Prototypes?
Where are you saying that?
I just said that.
Oh, another prototype.
I did it in color now.
Of course, there is also a life-threatening black, but this material is so wonderfully
stretchable.
It's just a cool color.
The next one.
Yes, that's a 36.
A small one.
Blue.
I found some interesting new designs and clothing today was really cool also the
fashion presentation yesterday was fun and to see everyone again say hi so I'm
saying goodbye to you I hope you liked this video check out my other stuff on
my channel and the links down below leave a comment bye